Hello everyone, good evening. So today with great
excitement we are introducing to you the
Max product of ICCL Lord, the newly launched health
insurance plan which everyone was waiting for a very long time because
ICCL Lord was not bringing that many innovative products in
health insurance for the last one or two years
and personally ICCL
Lord is one of my favorite
organization because the claim
settlement of ICCL Lord is extremely awesome. So today we will
talk about this newly launched product which
starts from basic sum insured of Rs. 1
crore and up to unlimited sum
insured option. Yes my dear this is the
first time in the insurance industry
after that you can go with unlimited sum
insured. Also this is a big solution for those people
who were always facing this problem in the future due to which problem they were
not able to take their decision that
which sum issue should I take because if
my age is 33 years today and in the coming 20
years  In 30 years, medical inflation will be very
high, so should I take a sum insured of one or two
crores?
For those people, the exact best option
is that it is unlimited sum insured. There are
options in this policy for 1 crore, 2 crores, 3 crores, 5
crores, 10 crores and limited sum insureds,
my dear, which makes this product the most
unique and my favorite too. But one
thing is that this policy is only for those people
who are purchasing a health insurance policy for the first time.
This policy does not allow
any portability.
This is a drawback or it
may be a pilot project of the company right now, hence
portability has not been allowed initially.
But the best part is unlimited sum insured. Yes,
my dear, follow by giving so many
features. Today we will talk in detail about this
product, which will go live tomorrow, December 7th,
for all the customers. So, for the first time,
this product review is on our youtube4
360 for all of you, specifically for the people,
for the young age group, even for  The age up to 65 years,
this is one of the best solution,
this policy comes with the two different options, one
is classic and second is the premium
plan, so we will talk about this product in full detail, so stay tuned to the
video,
follow the details that are coming on the screen in front of you and see
how many good things are there in this plan, that
first is unlimited sum insured product,
that means there is no tension of sum insured,
if in future there is any treatment cost of even Rs 20 crore for
any problem
after 20 years or 25 years, then there
is no such limit in this product, that means that
tension is over as to
how much sum should I take, second comes that if there is
unlimited sum insured, that means
its costing is very high, yes my dear, it has
affordable pricing and I will tell you its
pricing also at the end of the video, we will
take some examples of age, higher
age as well as lower age and I will tell you in detail about
pricing wise also  It is very
pocket friendly, it is a very good
product and thirdly it is a simple product, there is no much
confusion, it is not too much
fuss, it is
not very feature oriented but basically it covers all the things that should be
covered in health insurance
very well, this product is
ICC Lord Max
Protect, fourth it will come with two options
one is Classic and second is Premium so let me move
ahead and see
what other things are there in this Max
Protect product, so first one beats medical inflation
definitely when you have high sum insured
and there is also an option of
unlimited sum insured that means there is
no capping on sum insured so it
automatically beats inflation, no
coverage limit, no tension, no worries, access to
top health care, now you can get your treatment done even at the most expensive places,
you can avail the best hospital and best class services, with the
help of this policy you get coverage for
various medical expenses followed by world
wide coverage one of the best edition with low
premium this is a very good one
IC Lord has given a very good gift to its
consumers and the last rest reset
benefits which is also a cumulative bonus, which is
guaranteed 20 per year on year and it goes up
to 100%, so let's move ahead and talk about the features,
if we talk about the features of the classic plan, which is option one, that is,
in-patient day care, everything is covered, pre-
hospitalization 60 days and post-
hospitalization 180 days, which is the
standard which is generally covered by every company,
unlimited sum insured option, which
makes it unique, that is, there is no limit
of sum insured and the option which starts with
basic sum insured is one
crore, two crore, three crore, five crore, 10 crore
and
limits, now let's talk about guaranteed
cumulative bonus, 20 per claim free
year and max up to 200 per and AYUSH
treatment is also covered, this is also quite
common, donor and domis  Covered is up to sum
insured, dental surgery up to sum insured,
modern treatment up to sum insured and
maximum up to Rs. 10 crore. Here this capping is
put for domestic road ambulance with
in India. If we talk about domestic road ambulance,
that is cover for Rs.
100 and tele consultation is unlimited,
unlimited reset. Personally, I do
not believe in reset so much, but it is okay,
unlimited reset for any illness. Value
added services like health assistant, ambulance
deals and discounts, so many things which
these companies offer in this one of the
best plan and if we talk about premium plan, the
option to that offers is
worldwide cover and the worldwide cover is
up to sum insured up to Rs. 3 crore
maximum, which means that if
I have opted for my unlimited sum insured
under platinum, sorry, under premium plan, then
also I can enjoy up to Rs. 3 crore worldwide
and the
best part is that earlier ICICI
In Lombard policies, there used to be a
payment of 10% worldwide, that too there
is no co-payment of 10%, my dear, this is a very
good thing, let's talk further, air
ambulance, that is up to the sum insured, home
care treatment here is up to 1 lakh, which is okay, not so good right now, here
we can say a little weak, there is a claim
protector option, there is a preventive
health checkup up to ₹1000000, there
is an optional cover, if you want, you
can downgrade your room category,
where you take a single private
room, where you take a deluxe super deluxe
category, then
you get a
discount on the premium also, okay, but this
facility is only available in the classic
plan, there is also an option to wave off the PD waiting period, that is,
you can reduce it up
to 2 years, if we talk, still the zone
definition is given, but the
problem is still that the zone  If there is zone wise capping then the
recommendation is to pay zone one premium so that
this tension does not remain with us.
If we talk about zone A then
all the metro cities of Delhi come under zone A.
If we talk about zone B then Pune,
Kolkata, Telangana, Madhya Pradesh, Goa, Gujarat,
Bangalore, Chennai, Andhra Pradesh, Chhattisgarh,
Pacheri, Uttarakhand come under zone B.
If I talk about zone C then West of
India, Punjab,
Rajasthan, Chandigarh, Himachal Pradesh, Jammu and Kashmir, Ladakh, Lakshadweep, Kerala, Tamil Nadu, Odisha,
Arunachal Pradesh, Assam, Manipur, Meghalaya, Mizoram, Nagaland,
Tripuram, Sikkim, Jharkhand,
Maharashtra, UP excluding Mumbai and
Pune, it also comes under zone C. If we
talk about zone D then rest of
NCR and Noida, Jhajj, Jind, Nu, Panipat,
Wadi, Mewat all these come under zone D.
Okay, here there is zone wise capping as well,
my dear, we have to keep in mind that in the
pursuit of getting cheaper premium, we do
not adopt zone wise capping, hence it is better that
we pay zone one premium only and
avoid this tension, then we move ahead.
If we talk about term and condition, then
sum and short, as I told you earlier,
starting from 0 crore to unlimited sum in short,
eligibility is from six years to
65 years. We are eligible for this policy in adults
and children can
take individual plan from 91 days to 5 years. If
we talk about waiting period, then pre
assisting is four years but it can be reduced.
Waiting period for specific illness is two years. Standard
basic surgery has a waiting period of two years. Worldwide cover has a
waiting period of five years.
Talking about room limit, all rooms except suite category will
not be covered. After that,
excluding suite category, everything is
covered. And as we discussed earlier, if
we downgrade our stay to Option One, then
in single private room, we
also get a discount. Talking about tenure,
we can pay premium for one year, two years or three years
together, in which
we will also get long term discount.
On the second year, we will get 10%  On the first year and on the third year it is 15%.
This is one of the best thing I always
recommend. Please go for the third year's premium.
Now we can talk about zone wise classification.
So zone wise payment is applicable. So the
simple formula to avoid that is
please adopt zone one right. Medical
test. If we talk about underwriting, if the
PD is one, then it also depends whether
you are in North East or South East
and if your age is 55 or less and the
sum insured is Rs. 2 crore and above and there are more than two
PDs, then maybe they will ask for medical checkup. So there are
some such conditions.
So it depends on what is my medical
history and
from which state I am purchasing the policy and what is
my sum assured. It will depend on that. The
definition of South States is given as
Telangana, Karnataka, Andhra Pradesh, Tamil Nadu,
Kerala, Pachri, Lakshadweep and in East States it is given as
Orissa, West Bengal, Chhattisgarh, Jharkhand,
Bihar, Arunachal Pradesh, Assam, Manipur.  Meghalaya,
Mizoram, Nagaland, Tripura, Sikkim, Andaman
and Nicobar Islands, if we talk about the sum
insured up to 1 crore, only PD for
medical package. Home visit in case of PD
doctor can ask for higher package. Medical
grade will depend on the medical grade.
If I opt for a sum insured of only 1 crore, then
my normal medical checkup will be done.
Now if it is 1 crore, then PD for their medical package will be the
cost of the medical checkup. In
case the proposal
is accepted, if the proposal is rejected, then the
premium will be refunded after
deducting the medical charges as per the rate
chart. So, if the policy is rejected, then the
cost of health checkup will have to be
borne by you. BMI 35 is also under the age of
35. The
best part is that they are
also underwriting hypertension and diabetes.
If we talk about pricing, let me talk about my age.
That means 33 and if I take the
example of my family of two adults plus one
children, if we pay the premium of zone one
and choose the option of unlimited sum insured, then
how much
premium do I have to pay versus if I take a
sum insured of one crore zone wise in zone one, then
how much do I have to pay? If I opt for zone one and
opt for the 2 crore option
at the age of 33, then I have to pay 54000
approximately,
if I take the option of unlimited sum insured,
that means 10 crore plus, so
I have to pay only 60000, so there
is not much difference and the best part is
if we talk to any other competitor, then
in the same zone, 59000
approximately, 58 to 57000 is for Optima Secure for
2 CR and so many companies are like this, so
premium wise this is a very good product, so I
highly
recommend it, but I  Also encourage you before
buying a policy always find a right
intermediary please do not purchase
online because insurance means services and it is a
matter of services at the time of
most critical or such a time where I am in
physical, emotional or monetary trouble
in that situation I need someone who should take care of
all my formalities of claim and all so
please find a right intermediary and buy
policy with that
person so how did you like this product then please
tell me by commenting in the comment box
if you have any query then please tell me
still I will tell you one more thing here that
if after the higher age which I had promised
if we talk about 65 age for an adult for a
single adult then if they
take a sum insured of 9 crores and pay the premium of Zone One then the
premium they have to pay is
00 if they opt for unlimited sum
insured which
also has a foreign cover of 3 crores then
they have to pay the premium in that option  It is
approximate
again Fair edge pricing Edge per the edge and edge
per the sum insured How did you like the product? Do let us
know by commenting on the video and do
share the video with that friend who is a
fan of ICC Lumbard Must share with the
people Young people who are trying to find the best
health policy for them Stay connected Stay in
touch I wish you would have a right decision at
the right time All the best